Fixed Synced by bozxphd . Enjoy The Flick
- I 'm starting a new life .
Up here where it 's quiet and clean among the redwoods .
And almost no one knows me .
Poor Jerry .
I had a nervous breakdown after he left me .
They say I 'm cured now .
But I still have intrusive thoughts .
My therapist told me that I 'm not unusual at all .
People are abused all over the world
every day
much worse than me
and they do fine .
- Your tail light 's out , Miss .
- Oh , thank you for letting me know .
Are you gonna write me a ticket ?
- I 'll let you go this time , but make sure you get it fixed .
- Thank you , Officer .
- You drive safely .
- When Jerry left me , I devoured everything
I could about how to get your man back .
According to the experts , men are very fragile .
They can get crushed down if you assert yourself in any way .
You have to be very tricky .
- Elaine ?
Hi , I 'm Trish .
- Hi , Trish , it 's nice to meet you .
- Oh , you 're so pretty .
Oh , um , I didn 't mean anything .
I 'm married and everything .
- No , I didn 't think anything .
- Well , let me help you with your bags .
Is this all you 've got ?
- For now .
My art supplies are being shipped over later .
- So you 're an artist ?
- Yes , I am .
- I 'm an interior decorator .
- Oh , really ?
- Yes .
That 's how I met Barbara .
I decorated this apartment .
It was lucky I still had the keys .
Barbara didn 't exactly know when she 'd be back .
How do you know Barbara ?
- We used to dance together in San Francisco .
- Oh , really ?
Well , I hope you like the apartment .
It 's a bit garish but Barbara wanted it that way .
She had me take all of the colors from the Thoth Tarot deck
and she and her students did a bunch of occult paintings
for me to hang .
She 's into all that Wicca stuff .
Well , this is it .
- Oh , Trish , I love it .
It 's just beautiful .
- Really ?
Oh , I 'm so glad .
I thought I may have overdone it .
- Oh no , it 's exactly my taste .
- You must be exhausted .
I 'm sure you want to lie down .
- Actually , I was thinking about getting a bite to eat .
Do you know of a place around here ?
- There 's the Victorian Tea Room .
We could go together , if you don 't mind the company .
- Oh , how fantastic .
Where can I freshen up ?
- The bedroom is through there .
- I 'll only be a moment .
- What a lovely room .
- Yes , isn 't it ?
I love Victoriana .
- Being here is like being a princess in a fairy tale .
- Do you have fairy princess fantasies , Elaine ?
- Of course .
We may be grown women , but underneath
we 're just little girls dreaming about being carried off
by a prince on a white horse .
- Yes , I suppose so .
It 's ridiculous , isn 't it ?
- I don 't think I 've found my Prince Charming yet ,
but I think I found the formula .
You know , I 've been studying parapsychology
and I understand men so much better than I used to .
If only I would have known before what I know now .
Then Jerry would have never left me .
- Who 's Jerry ?
- My ex-husband .
The day he left me was the day that I died .
But then I was reborn as a witch .
Barbara and Gahan brought me back to life .
They taught me everything I know about magic and about men .
Men are like children .
They 're very easy to please
as long as we give them what they want .
♫ Tra la la la
♫ Tra la la la la di da
♫ I dreamed of a fairy lady in a strange land
♫ She captured the hearts of all the boys and men
♫ She wore a gown
♫ Of pink and purple roses
♫ It was so tra la la and so la di da ♫
- Where were we ?
Oh , men , you said we need to give them what they want .
Well , what do men want ?
- Just a pretty woman to love and to take care of them
and to make them feel like a man
and to give them total freedom
in whatever they wanna do or be .
- But what about what we want ?
How are we going to be equals with men
if we keep catering to all of their needs ?
- I think that if you want love , you have to give love .
Giving men sex is a way of unlocking their love potential .
- You sound as if you 'd been brainwashed by the patriarchy .
Your whole self-worth is wrapped up in pleasing a man .
I 'll admit , I used sex to get this ,
but I 'm not proud of it .
A whole world doesn 't revolve around a man 's needs .
If I gave Richard sex every time he wanted it ,
I 'd be a wreck .
- Poor Richard .
He loves you and he wants you and you torture him .
You have to give a man his fantasy .
- His fantasy ?
- Yes , his fantasy .
But what I 'm really interested in
is love .
You might say I 'm addicted to love .
I wonder if all women feel that way ?
- Well , it depends on what you mean by love .
A husband isn 't a prince , Elaine ,
and life isn 't a fairy tale .
We have to face that fact .
- Why ?
Maybe life could be a fairy tale
if you pleased your husband more .
- I don 't need to please Richard .
Richard loves me for myself .
- Of course .
Perhaps you did find your Prince Charming .
- Perhaps I did .
- Guess who .
- Richard , what are you doing here ?
This tea room is for ladies only .
- Oh , I went to visit you at work
and Julie said you were here .
I thought we could have lunch together .
- Well , that 's very sweet , but I 've already had my lunch .
Oh , uh , Richard , this is Elaine .
Elaine , this is my husband , Richard .
- I 've heard so much about you , Richard .
- Nothing too horrible , I hope .
- On the contrary .
- Goddess , please ,
send me a beautiful , sweet man
to love me as I love him .
To love me , love me ,
love me ,
love me .
Hi , are you Wendy ?
- Yes , what can I do for you ?
- I 'm Elaine .
We spoke on the phone .
I make natural soaps and candles and things .
- Elaine , right .
Thanks for coming by .
Mind if I have a look ?
- Please do .
- These are nice .
Really nice .
I think these will do well in the store .
- Then you 'll take them ?
- Let 's start with these and see how they do .
If these sell in the next week or two , I 'll order more .
Sound good ?
- Yes , fantastic .
Thank you , Wendy .
- Sure , Elaine .
Bright blessings .
- People always ask me why I 'm a witch .
I tell them it 's because I want to have magical powers .
But it 's not like it sounds .
All it is is using your will to get what you want .
- Hi .
- It 's a beautiful day .
- Yes , it is .
I love to be out in nature on days like this .
- Oh , you like nature ?
- Very much .
You seem like a nature type too .
I 'll bet you like to spend time in the woods .
- That 's right .
How 'd you know ?
- I can just tell .
Nature is where your heart is .
City and people can get to be too much for you .
- Whuh , that is a lot to get from someone in a few seconds .
- I 'm talented that way .
- Well , you 're right about the city .
In fact , I have a house out in the woods
about an hour from here .
I like to go there whenever I can to , you know ,
just think and read .
- Do you take your wife up there ?
- No .
I 'm not married .
- Well , you might at least take a girl up there
once in a while .
- I do .
I do , once in a while .
- You wanna take a girl up there now ?
What do you mean ?
- Well , I 'm new in town
and I haven 't seen much of the nature around here .
I 'll make you a nice dinner .
- Yes , okay , sure .
Uh , my car is right over there .
- Okay .
Let 's go .
You know what I 'd like to do right now ?
I 'd like to make love right here in the car
just like we were kids .
- Wait , wait .
You want some ?
- What is it ?
- Something I made .
- Mm .
Oh , wo , ho , ho , ho , that is , that is strong .
- Finish it .
- Oh .
- No , Wayne , Wayne , stop .
Not here .
Let 's go inside .
This is beautiful .
I 'll start the dinner .
- Wow .
This looks delicious .
- To nature .
- This is really nice , isn 't it ?
I like to come up here a lot
at the end of the semester to unwind .
- Are you a teacher ?
- Yeah , I teach at the university .
- Oh , what do you teach ?
- English and French literature
with a focus on the 18th century .
- So , you must be quite a libertine .
- A libertine ?
Why would you say that ?
- Oh , you know .
All of the dangerous liaisons , Fanny Hill stuff .
Not to mention Casanova .
- Well , there were a lot of books written
in the 18th century .
- Well , is it true ?
Are you a libertine ?
- Yes I am .
I love women .
Does that bother you ?
- On the contrary .
Oh , hmm ,
I feel strange , dizzy .
What was in that drink you gave me ?
- Organic berries , vodka , hallucinogenic herbs .
- Hallucinogenic herbs ?
Oh , baby .
You are really wild .
- Would you mind if I made myself more comfortable ?
- Not at all .
♫ La ♫
- What the hell ?
Your coat .
It 's so bright .
♫ La ♫
- I always line my clothing .
- You have two selves .
Dark and quiet that you show the world .
Who do you give that to ?
The rainbow ?
- I give the rainbow to you .
Right now .
♫ La ♫
♫ La la la ♫
- Oh .
♫ La la ♫
- Huh !
Oh God .
Oh , Elaine .
Look at you .
- You can make love to me now .
♫ La la la la ♫
- Aw , okay .
- What is it , Wayne ?
What is it , baby ?
- Oh , Elaine , I feel so strange .
- It 's all right , you 're with me , shhh .
- Elaine .
No woman has ever given herself like that to me before .
- Life has been tough , huh ?
- Yeah , in a way .
You 're not like any other woman I 've met .
No games , no agendas .
You just seem to take life as it is .
- Is there any other way to take life ?
- Well , the women I 've been with ,
they all want you to make a bunch of promises to ' em
as soon as you sleep with ' em .
But , how can you commit to someone that you don 't even know ?
It 's crazy .
- I know , baby .
I know .
- I never thought I wanted to be tied down to anybody .
But it 's just ' cause no one was ever quite right .
All the women that I 'm attracted to physically
they 're never bright enough .
And all the bright ones are homely and don 't arouse me .
- That seems like quite a problem .
- It is .
I feel my whole life as a loner ,
thinkin ' I didn 't need anybody .
But now I 'm not so sure .
Oh , Elaine ,
I have never felt real love like this before .
- You 're just having a lot of emotions right now .
- Oh .
Elaine , I 'm scared .
I 'm not used to feeling things so strongly .
I can 't take it , I can 't take it .
Oh .
Elaine , I 'm sick .
I 'm sick .
- Hey , it 's all right .
I 've got you .
I love you .
And I 'll always be here for you .
Try to get some sleep .
- Elaine .
Elaine , where are you ?
- What a pussy .
What a baby .
I thought I 'd found a real man ,
but he 's just like a little girl .
- Elaine !
- No one was ever there for me
when I was crying my heart out .
No one ever comforted me .
No one .
- Good morning , Wayne .
- Hi , Elaine .
- Here , drink this .
- I had such horrible dreams last night .
- What did you dream about , baby .
- I dreamt that I was calling your name
and you didn 't answer .
I kept calling and calling , but I couldn 't find you .
Oh , Elaine , you love me , don 't you ?
- Of course , I love you .
- Oh God , oh God , Elaine .
- Are you hungry ?
- I don 't know what I am .
- Well , try to get some sleep .
- Elaine .
Don 't leave me .
- I 'm not going anywhere , baby .
I 'll be right here .
Wayne , wake up .
It 's late .
Wayne .
Wayne , baby , wake up .
Wake up .
Wayne .
- Tampons aren 't gross .
Women bleed and that 's a beautiful thing .
Do you know that most men have never even seen a used tampon ?
Part of me can be with Wayne now .
Always .
I don 't really mind death .
I 've buried people before .
People I really cared about .
In the end we 're all just compost anyway .
Everything regenerates .
I 'd like to come back as a cat .
I 've been so depressed since my cat died .
His name was Greymalkin , but he was black and white .
He was my best friend .
- I give the rainbow to you .
Right now .
Just a minute .
Oh hi Trish .
Come on in .
- Hey , Elaine .
You look gorgeous .
I love what you 've done with your hair .
- Thank you .
What 's up , honey ?
- Well , I haven 't been able to reach you ,
so I thought I 'd come over
to see if everything was all right .
- I 'm fine .
Really .
Can I offer you something ?
I just made some tea and cake .
- Just tea , thank you .
- Cream and sugar ?
- No , I 'm fine , thank you .
So , what have you been so busy with ?
A man , I hope .
- Yes , it was a man .
But , it didn 't work out .
- I 'm Sorry .
- Yes , it 's a shame and I really liked him .
I thought that he was the one .
- Well , maybe next time .
- Are you sure you won 't have some cake ?
- Oh , no , thank you .
I just came over to check up on you and to say good bye .
- Good bye ?
Why , where are you going ?
- Oh , just to Dallas for a furniture convention .
- Is Richard going with you ?
- No , it 's just a business trip .
Richard will have to fend for himself for awhile .
- Sam , give me two whiskeys on the rocks .
- Sure thing , Jane .
Did you see the papers today ?
- No , why ?
- They found a body in the Eel River .
- A murder ?
- Maybe .
They found a symbol carved in his chest .
Here .
- It 's a pentagram .
- It 's them witches again .
- That 's what I was thinking too , Lyle .
- So yeah , Barbara , that 's everything .
After Jerry died , the cops wouldn 't stop harassing me .
They couldn 't prove anything .
They actually thought that I killed him .
Can you believe it ?
Anyways , San Francisco got to be a really bad trip
after you left .
That 's when I remembered you had that extra apartment .
- Well , it was perfect timing .
I 'm just sorry I wasn 't here to greet you .
That 's all right .
Trish has been lovely .
And I 've been getting a lot of artwork done .
But I had this experience last weekend
that really shook me up .
- Why , what happened ?
- Well , I met this great-looking guy .
And I used love magic on him .
Then he got really weird on me .
All these emotions started flowing out of him .
Then he got really
sick .
- Well , guys can 't handle their emotions too well .
That 's why they don 't like heavy conversations .
It was probably just too much for him .
All the love and the great sex that you were giving him .
- I guess that 's what it was .
But , I don 't know .
- Honey , you have to be more careful .
Maybe you shouldn 't be messing with love spells
in the first place , you know .
- Merry Meet , Elaine .
- Bright blessings Gahan .
- I heard you discussing love spells .
You do have to be careful , Elaine .
Love spells never work the way you think they will .
But on a lighter note , it 's wonderful to see you , Elaine .
What 's it been now , a year ?
We must celebrate this reunion of dear friends .
Thank you , Goddess , everywhere ,
for the blessings that we share .
- Blessed be , Hurrahya !
- Go home , witches .
Go home .
- Just ignore them .
They 're always giving us trouble .
- I didn 't know this town was hostile to witches .
- Well , it 's certainly not San Francisco .
But it 's not bad for a small town .
Not all of them embrace our methods
of practicing witchcraft .
But , I don 't see why we ought to be so uptight now .
Back in the day , we all made love freely
and put up Baphomet posters and no one was dogmatic
about whether they were a witch or a Satanist or a Thelemite
or a Druid or a Wiccan or whatever .
And it was fun .
But our classes and circles have been very popular .
- What have you been teaching ?
- Let 's see , I 've got a new class on sigil magic
and Barbara 's got a new class on organite alchemy .
Otherwise , we 're still teaching the staples ,
energy grounding , Earth-based spirituality ,
pagan arts and crafts ,
candle work , the spellcraft master class , ancient mysticism ,
herbs and spices , and sex magic , of course .
- Oh , are you still teaching that ?
- Yes , in fact , we 've invited some girls here tonight
for a seminar about the power of sexual dancing .
Dancing is such a powerful thing for women and girls .
- Are you still dancing ?
- Yeah , some of us dance here on Amateur Night .
You should come .
- Hi , Barbara .
Hi , Gahan .
Sorry we 're late .
- Hello lovely ladies , please have a seat .
Elaine , this is Star and her sister Moon .
They 're our students for tonight .
Girls , this is our dear friend Elaine .
- Hi .
- I was just pointing out that dancing
is a powerful thing for women and girls .
We asked you to meet us here tonight
so you could learn about that .
Do you see how powerful that girl is ?
These men would do anything for her .
Wouldn 't you like to have that power yourselves ?
Then let us begin .
All witches need to figure out where their power lies .
And we feel that a woman 's greatest power
lies in her sexuality .
We don 't view this power as Satanic or anti-feminist ,
but as a celebration of woman as a natural creature .
An earthly body , a spiritual essence , and a womb .
- The whole history of witchcraft is interwoven
with the fear of female sexuality .
They burned us at the stake because they feared
the erotic feelings we elicited in them .
Later , they used marriage to hold us in bondage
and made us into servants , whores , and fantasy dolls
never asking us what we wanted .
- They teach us that a normative human being
is a hyper-rationalist , stoic male
and that women 's emotions and intuitions are illnesses
that need to be cured .
And we believe that men and women are different
and that true equality lies in that difference .
- We strive for male / female polarity and to regain
our primal power as goddesses .
We need to teach men how to love us
using ways they can understand .
So goddesses , use perfume ,
wear high heels and makeup ,
learn to dress your hair in attractive ways ,
display flesh artfully , and know what to conceal .
Be a mother and a lover .
Stand your ground , but always let the man feel like a man .
- Use sex magic to destroy his fear of you
and to open his heart to the floodgates of love .
Only then will he begin to see you as a human being
with all of your inner beauty .
Then , when his heart is open to love ,
you may do with him what you will .
- I love you , Elaine .
You know that , don 't you ?
I love you very much .
But you need to be more careful .
Dinner was late three times this week .
And that house is a total pigsty .
Do you know that I found an old hot dog
under the bed this morning ?
And why don 't you ever brush your hair ?
You need to take better care of yourself and of the house .
I 'm embarrassed to have people over .
I 've been really patient up until now ,
but you need to step up your game .
- I have a crazy bitch for a daughter .
What ?
You 're not crazy ?
Well , if you 're not crazy then you 're stupid .
Which is it ?
Are you crazy or are you stupid ?
And you could lose a few pounds .
You 're looking a little fatty .
- Oh my God , Elaine , you 've lost so much weight .
You have such a hot body now .
Do you like it when I touch you like this ?
Or like this ?
I wanna make you come .
- Don 't be frightened , Elaine .
I would never hurt you .
I 'm not the big , bad wolf .
You need to have perfect love and perfect trust .
- Hast thou the courage to make the essay ?
- I have two words , perfect love and perfect trust .
- Assist me to erect the ancient altar
at which in days past all worshiped .
For in the old times , a woman was the altar .
And the sacred place was the point within the center
of the circle , the origin of all things .
Therefore , should we adore it .
- Good morning , Sergeant Griff .
Congratulations on your promotion .
- Thanks , Connie .
Is there any coffee .
- Yeah , I just made some .
I made it just the way you like it .
- Is there anything you don 't do well ?
- Why don 't you try me sometime and find out ?
- How 's the coffee , Steve ?
- Uh , too strong .
- Well , I like it strong .
Man 's gotta stay awake on the job after all .
- Why , have you been keeping late nights ?
- Maybe so .
- But , now that you 've been promoted ,
maybe you ought to start thinking about settling down .
- Me , you kidding ?
- Sergeant Meadows , a lady 's here to see you .
- I 'm Shelly Curtis .
I phoned about Wayne Peters , the teacher who disappeared .
- Yes , of course .
Have a seat , Miss Curtis .
You say you think Mr. Peters might have been kidnapped ?
- Yes , no one 's seen him for two weeks .
I went by his house and the mail 's piled up .
We had lunch the day he disappeared .
I saw him drive away with a strange woman near the plaza .
- Do you have any idea where he might have gone with her ?
- Wayne used to spend weekends
up in a cabin he had in the woods .
He used to take dates there .
- Oh , Jesus .
♫ La ♫
- Hey Griff , look .
- Good lord .
♫ La ♫
- What the hell is this ?
- I don 't know .
We 're going to have to dig , Steve .
- I know .
♫ La ♫
I think you should go back to the house , Shelly .
- Mmm , mmm ,
this cake is absolutely fantastic .
And what a great dinner .
- Thank you .
I enjoy cooking .
Hope you don 't mind my calling you .
Sometimes it 's so hard to be alone .
- Not at all .
I get a little lonely , too , when Trish is out of town .
- How long have you and Trish been married ?
- 10 years this September .
- 10 years !
It 's really amazing .
No one has ever loved me the way you love Trish , no one .
- What about your husband ?
- My husband never loved me .
He couldn 't wait to get away from me .
- I 'm sorry .
Sometimes I think Trish would like to get away from me , too .
- Poor baby .
Poor , poor baby .
So , tell me , what turns you on ?
- What turns me on ?
Wow , no one 's ever asked me that before .
Let me think .
You know what really turns me on ?
Flying .
- Flying ?
- Yeah , flying a plane .
You don 't know what kinda high it is .
You 're soarin ' up there above everything .
You 're in control .
- Oh , how fantastic .
- It really is .
It 's the only time I feel really clear about things .
Sometimes I look at my life and I wonder how I got here .
I feel like my life is slipping away
and there 's so many things I haven 't done .
- Like what ?
- I 've never had any sordid love affairs
or gotten into any mischief .
I used to watch those old Steve McQueen movies ,
you know , the ones where they 'd rob a bank or something ,
and I 'd fantasize that I was one of those
crazy kinda gangsters with a sexy , messed up girl on my arm .
Or those Westerns , when they 'd shoot up a town
and then go visit the local prostitutes .
It 's sounds stupid , I know .
- No , it doesn 't .
It 's very sweet .
- Really ?
Trish doesn 't think so .
She just rolls her eyes when I talk like this .
- That 's because she doesn 't understand you .
I understand you perfectly .
- You do ?
- Of course .
You wanna have a sordid love affair .
You wanna get into some mischief .
- Uh .
- Ho !
Who are you ?
What are you doing to me ?
- I 'm the love witch .
I 'm your ultimate fantasy .
- That 's right .
That 's right .
- Steve , I 'm going out to see that witch doctor .
- Who ?
- Professor King .
He specializes in black magic and witchcraft .
He might be able to help me
identify some of the items we found .
- It 's great .
Did you get the lab report ?
- Yeah , yeah , it looks like heart failure .
But the toxicology report showed traces of Jimson weed
also known as Devil 's weed , a highly toxic hallucinogenic .
- It 's unbelievable .
You want me to come with you ?
- No , this will only take a few minutes .
Can you order me a turkey and avocado on whole wheat ?
- Mustard , mayo ?
- Yeah and cole slaw .
Thanks .
- Done .
- Ah , Sergeant Meadows , sorry to have kept you waiting .
- Glad to meet you , Professor .
Professor , this is the bottle we found in a grave
of Wayne Peters , the one you read about in the paper .
- Interesting , yes .
Just as I thought .
The contents indicate that it 's a witch bottle .
- A witch bottle ?
- Yes , witches used to make them
for protection against curses .
They 'd take something personal like bodily fluids or hair
along with herbs and something sharp
like pins or broken glass to scare away evil spirits .
Witch bottles have often been found buried in the hearths
of very old houses .
- Would it be safe to assume that the person who made this
was a witch ?
- It 's very likely .
Witchcraft , long dormant in civilized places ,
has taken root again in cities .
There have several rituals per year .
One of them , Samhain , corresponds of our Halloween .
Other rituals celebrate Summer Solstice , Litha ,
or the Winter Solstice , which they call Imbolg .
Here the members of a coven kiss the devil 's behind
in a mockery of Christian rituals .
Here , a satanic cult sacrifices a child .
- Does this stuff really go on today ?
- Yes , indeed .
Those who practice human sacrifice are the black witches
who perform blood rituals to gain demonic powers
and to bind their members together in secrecy .
Law has been trying to root out these cults for decades
but they 've been unsuccessful .
Then there are the white witches or Wiccans
who commune in nature in the healing spirit
and who have a strict law that forbids harming others .
Every city and rural village today has pockets
of both black and white witches
who practice the ancient rites .
- I invoke and call upon thee , Mighty Mother of us all .
I invoke thee to descend upon the body of this thy servant
and priestess .
- Of the Mother Darksome and Divine
here I charge you in this sign .
- Listen to the words of the Great Mother .
She , who of old , who was also called Artemis ,
Aphrodite , Cerridwen , Diana , Isis ,
and by many other names .
- Whenever ye have need of anything ,
then ye shall assemble in some secret place and adore me ,
who am Queen of all witches .
There shall ye assemble , ye who are fain to learn
all sorcery .
Behold all acts of love and pleasure are my rituals .
Behold I have been with thee from the beginning
and I am that which is attained at the end of desire .
Bagabi lacha bachabe .
Lamac cahi achababe .
Hurrahya ! Hurrahya !
- Arise .
Eko , Eko , Azarak
Eko , Eko , Zomelak
Eko , Eko , Cernunnos
Eko , Eko , Aradia !
- You 're looking a little tense tonight , love .
What 's the matter ?
- Oh nothing , just my usual roller coaster love life .
- Well , have a drink and relax .
Nothing 's that dire , at least not for you .
It 's an entirely different story for your victims .
- What victims ?
- There 's no need to play Miss Innocent with me , dearie .
- Please , don 't touch me .
- Bright blessings , Barbara .
- Merry meet , Elaine .
How 's it going ?
- I 'm back in the dating pool again .
- What happened ?
I thought you were crazy about that new guy you were seeing ,
the married man .
- No , I broke it off .
He just became really obsessive , morose ,
and his aura became really murky .
He didn 't even wanna make love anymore .
He became just like a woman , crying at every little thing .
There was no polarity .
But , I should have known .
He 's a Pisces .
- Richard ?
- I thought I told you never to interrupt me
when I 'm working .
What do you want ?
- I just wanted to let you know that I 'm going to bed
and I 'm taking a pill .
Are you coming to bed ?
- No .
I have some more work to do .
- All right , see you tomorrow , then .
♫ La ♫
♫ La la la la ♫
- Sergeant Griff Meadows of the Police Department .
I 'd like to ask you a few questions .
- Okay .
- Does this look familiar to you ?
- It 's a witch bottle .
- Do you have any idea who could have made it ?
- No , no I don 't .
- Ever seen any of these in here before ?
- Yeah , we have some witch bottles .
I 'll show you one .
Here 's one .
- How common are these bottles ?
- I 've never seen ' em in here before until
a girl started supplying ' em to us .
- Who is this girl ?
- Her name is Elaine , Elaine Parks .
- Who is it ?
- Sergeant Meadows , Police Department .
Sorry to bother you , ma 'am , but I 'm investigating a case
and I just wanted to ask you a few questions .
- About what ?
- Well , it 's a potential homicide case .
Just a routine check .
I thought you might be able to help us .
- Of course .
Please come in , Sergeant .
So you say there was a homicide .
How horrible .
Who was killed ?
- A man named Wayne Peters .
Did you know Wayne Peters ?
- No .
- Here 's a picture of him .
Ever seen him before ?
- No .
I guess I can 't help you , Sergeant .
Good bye .
- Ms. Parks , wait .
Have you ever seen anything like this before ?
- It 's a Magic Bottle .
I made it myself .
- Have you ever seen one containing urine ?
- Urine ?
No .
- We found this bottle containing urine and a used tampon
on the grave of Wayne Peters .
- Will you excuse me for a moment , Sergeant ?
- Ms. Parks , are you a witch ?
- Yes , I am .
Is there a law against that ?
- I guess not , not unless you do something wrong .
- Do you think that being a witch makes me evil ,
capable of murder even ?
- No , I wasn 't trying to imply ...
- Sergeant Meadows , do you know what it 's like
to really suffer ?
You have to fight and fight
until you 're too exhausted to go on .
Witchcraft is my religion , Sergeant .
And this religion , which is older than your Christianity ,
saved my life .
- Ms. Parks , I 'm sorry if I 've offended you .
I didn 't realize .
- That 's all right , Sergeant Meadows .
- You can call me Griff .
- Griff ?
I know I 've seen you before .
I just don 't know where .
- I have that same feeling .
- I know .
You 're the man in the cards .
You 're my fate .
- What do you mean , I 'm your fate ?
- I did a Celtic Cross reading .
For my future card I got Knight of Wands .
Always felt that if that card showed up in a future reading ,
I would soon meet the man that I 'm going to marry .
But , the man that I marry has to love animals .
Do you like animals , Griff ?
- Why yes , I love animals .
In fact , a friend of mine has a couple horses
I 'm very fond of .
You know , tomorrow is my day off
and it 's supposed to be quite nice out .
Maybe I 'll get away from the city and do some riding .
Do you like to ride , Elaine ?
Whoa .
- Oh Patchouli , you 're such a sweetheart .
- How 's my girl ?
- Am I your girl ?
- For today you are .
You 're my girl and there 's nobody around
to tell me otherwise .
- Except me .
- And what 's that supposed to mean ?
- Nothing .
Kiss me .
- What 's that sound ?
- I don 't know .
Let 's go see .
- Now is the time of the Summer Solstice .
The strength of the Oak King is waning .
And the Holly King stands ready to challenge him
for the hand of the Green Maiden .
- Let the battle begin .
- Your season is over old man .
- Oh never .
- I will have her .
- Never have her .
- Never .
- Holly King , I name you the victor .
The Green Maiden is yours .
- M 'lady .
Come on .
- Elaine .
- You know these people ?
- Well yes , in a way .
- All hail , fair Lord and Lady .
Welcome to our little gathering .
- All hail .
- We are the good people of the Renaissance
and Medieval players and we are celebrating the Midsummer .
Won 't you join us ?
- To be sure , fair consorts .
- They are charming , are they not ?
- Yes , quite charming .
- I see two people in love .
This calls for a wedding .
- A wedding ?
- Yes , a mock wedding , if you will .
To honor the gods of love .
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Love will make you feel like a Queen or a King
♫ Unicorns , rainbows , lucky charms
♫ Await you in your true love 's arms
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Mystical , physical , alchemical
♫ We 're pretending to be in love today
♫ But pretending is also real
♫ There 's a lady in a castle
♫ She 's sad and so forlorn
♫ When her troubadour returns and kisses her
♫ She 's all smiles and laughter
♫ Lady , you 're so beautiful
♫ Come lie with me and be my love
♫ I 'd slay any dragon , endure any danger
♫ Just to have you near me
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Lucky lovers mate in the spring
♫ We sip from goblets full of joy
♫ But when love dies all life it does destroy ♫
- Okay .
- Now , ye are wed .
- I 'm so happy for you , Elaine , he 's adorable .
- I 'm not in love .
It 's not that I don 't have sentiment ,
it 's just that love is soft .
You need guts in this business .
I 've seen guys get shot to death because they fell in love
and got soft inside .
I want an heir some day
and then I would need to have a wife ,
but love is something else .
A man can get destroyed by things like that .
It 's like he 's not even a man anymore .
I never wanna get like that .
- When you really love him ,
it 's like fireworks and nothing else matters .
You love all the little quirks about him .
The way he slurps his cereal .
The way his mouth is a little crooked .
Those details about him become your whole life .
Something inside you opens up like a flower
and you realize that you have more love to give
than you ever thought was possible .
'Cause the more you know him ,
the more you love him .
- The more you get to know a woman ,
the less you can feel about her .
At first , she 's this incredible object of mystery
who fulfills all you 're wildest fantasies .
Then she starts to reveal little flaws
and after a while , just gets pretty hard to care .
Feminine ideal only exists in a man 's mind .
No woman could ever fulfill it .
And sometimes , when she tries to love you more ,
give you more , you feel like you 're suffocating ,
drowning in estrogen .
The most awful feeling .
- Dinner tonight , Griff ?
- Um , can 't tonight , Connie .
Some other time .
- Hey Griff , I got more information
on that Elaine Parks girl .
- You leave it on my desk .
- Don 't you wanna hear it ?
- Steve , Captain wants us to lay off the case .
- Are you serious ?
- He says we have a policy of leaving the witches alone .
He says they 've lived in this town a long time
and he doesn 't like to mess with them .
- Even if they murder ?
- He says he 's satisfied that Wayne 's death
was a heart attack .
I think so too .
- Has everyone gone crazy around here ?
Let me at least tell you what I found .
Now , Elaine used to run an organic beauty store
in Berkeley with her husband , Jerry .
Two years later they were divorced
and Elaine moved to San Francisco
to start dancing at a burlesque club
where she got involved with a witch coven .
The coven broke up after police questioning
when some of it 's members died mysteriously .
Soon after , Elaine 's ex-husband died of a drug overdose
shortly before he was planning to remarry .
The police questioned Elaine
but they couldn 't find enough to hold her .
- Well , if the San Francisco Police couldn 't find anything ,
what happened there is none of our business .
- Are you serious ?
- I 'd say this woman is a dangerous character
and you better watch her .
- You mean because she 's a witch ?
That doesn 't mean anything .
- No , her husband died of a drug he 'd never taken before .
And did you ever find where Wayne Peters
got the Devil 's weed ?
- I questioned Ms. Curtis about that .
There was Devil 's weed growing near his cabin .
Apparently , he experimented often with drugs .
- Come on Griff , can 't you connect the dots ?
We have a possible murder here
and Elaine is our only suspect .
- I told you , we 're laying off her .
- Because of orders or because you 're in love with her ?
- Who says I 'm in love with her ?
Get the hell off my back .
- You 're out of line , Griff , way out of line .
- Richard .
Richard !
- Thank you for meeting me , Elaine .
It 's not good for me to be alone too much .
I know you 're busy .
- Of course .
I wanted to come .
- I can 't help but blaming myself for what happened .
- You can 't blame yourself .
You were a good wife to Richard .
- I tried to be .
I tried so hard to please him ,
but I should have tried harder .
He wanted a certain type of woman , someone I could never be .
Maybe you were right .
Maybe you should give a man his fantasy .
I thought that was so awful when you said that .
Maybe I was being naive ,
but I really thought he loved me for me .
But now , now I wish ...
- You have to stop torturing yourself .
You have to let go .
Remember how he changed after my Dallas trip ?
I think that 's when he started having that affair .
Whoever she was she drove him crazy .
I hated him so much for that .
I wanted to kill them both .
If I ever found out who she was , I would rip her to pieces .
But now I see I should have helped him .
I didn 't know that he was going to take his own life .
- Hey ,
hey .
- Enough about me .
What 's going on with you ?
- Trish , I 'm in love .
- Who is he ?
- He 's a detective and he 's everything
a woman could ever want .
He 's strong and handsome , smart and kind .
I just know that he 's the one .
He even gave me this ring .
I call it my magic ring .
It 's not an engagement ring
but I just know that he 's gonna pop the question soon .
- When we first came here
I showed you my engagement ring , remember ?
I can barely stand to look at it anymore .
It 's too painful .
I 'm sure he 's going to ask you soon .
You 're going to make a beautiful bride .
The first day we met ,
you were envious of me because I had a man
and you were all alone .
Now it 's the reverse .
Life is funny , isn 't it ?
- Trish , I 'm sorry , I 've gotta go .
Would you like to walk out with me ?
- No , I 'd like to stay and finish my tea .
- All right .
Take care , love .
- Hi Elaine , it 's me .
Yeah , you left your ring here .
You 're probably driving but I 'll drop it by on my way home .
See you in a minute .
♫ La
♫ la la la la la
♫ La la la la la ♫
- You bitch .
You killed my husband .
Bitch , skank , whore .
You 'll burn for this .
- Crash , crash , crash .
Die , die , die .
Eko , Eko , Azarak !
Eko , Eko , Zomelak !
Eko , Eko , Aradia !
Eko , Eko , Azarak !
Eko , Eko , Zomelak !
- Oh Habondia , bind these two
with a heady lovers ' brew .
Even should they strive to flee
they 'll cling for all eternity .
- Scotch .
- Bottle o ' beer , Sam .
Who are those new girls ?
They can 't dance at all .
And they 're weird .
- I don 't know , but the customers really like ' em .
- They 're friends of the witches .
I seen them come in together before .
- Yeah , the witches .
They 're everywhere .
- One gin and tonic , Sam .
- Gin and tonic coming up .
- Did you read about the teacher
buried in the back yard of his cabin ?
They said it was done by the witches .
- Oh yeah , I read about that .
They found all kinds of witchcraft things on the grave .
- Yeah , I heard about that , too .
Creepy .
- Sit down , Elaine .
Elaine , the DNA came back from the lab .
It connects you with Wayne Peters .
Patricia Manning came by the station .
With some things of yours .
Including this .
She said you drove her husband to suicide .
- So , I was a bad girl .
Are you going to punish me ?
- What sort of person are you , Elaine ?
What sort of sick mind would do such things ?
- Why are you so negative ?
I didn 't kill anyone .
Wayne died of heart failure
after a beautiful night of lovemaking .
And Richard died because he loved me too much .
These men weren 't used to the deep feelings of love
that they were experiencing with me .
- Are you saying these men died of love ?
That 's insane .
What about the spells and the drugs ?
Are you saying witchcraft had nothing to do with it ?
- Witchcraft is just a way of concentrating energy .
It can only work with what 's already there .
I just use sex magic to create love magic .
I didn 't know how strong the spells would be .
Sometimes it 's almost scary how strong the love gets .
- Love ?
What do you know about love ?
What you call love is a borderline personality disorder
or worse .
- Don 't diagnose me .
Maybe you 're a narcissist who can 't love .
You think that I 'm sick
because you 've never loved like I have .
Well , I would do anything for love .
- That 's right , you 'll never get enough love .
Even when a man loves you so much it kills him ,
it 's not enough for you .
You 're like a bottomless hole .
You doll yourself up and do the Stepford Wife thing
thinking every man is going to fall at your feet .
But your creepy little sexy act doesn 't work with me .
I don 't love you .
- How can you stand there and boast
about being immune to love ?
Why does the genuine love of a woman scare you so much ?
You think that your way is a superior way to live ?
I know a lot of women who feel the way that I do .
Only men make us work so hard for your love .
If you would just love us for ourselves ,
but you won 't .
My ex-husband was just like you .
He used to punish me by withholding his love from me .
All my life I 've been tossed in the garbage
except when men wanted to use my body .
So , I decided to find my own power .
And I found that power through witchcraft .
That means that I take what I need from men
and not the other way around .
- I 'm sorry , Elaine .
It won 't work this time .
I 'm afraid I 'm going to have to arrest you .
- What for ?
Marrying a lover according to my religion ?
Seducing a married man ?
I know 400 years ago you could be burned
for a thing like that , but not today .
- No , not burned ,
but you 'll be booked for burying Wayne Peters illegally
and we 'll find out more .
- Oh , that 's the witch who killed the teacher .
- Thou shalt not suffer a witch to live .
- Burn the witch .
- Burn the witch , burn the witch , burn the witch ,
burn the witch , burn the witch , burn the witch ,
burn the witch , burn the witch , burn the witch .
- Burn !
- Burn her .
- Burn .
Burn .
- Poor baby .
Poor , poor baby .
Don 't worry , everything will be okay
because I love you so much .
♫ La
♫ la la la la la
♫ La la la la la ♫
- I love you , Elaine .
I 've never loved anyone but you .
I want to marry you .
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Love will make you feel like a Queen or a King
♫ Unicorns , rainbows , lucky charms
♫ Await you in your true love 's arms
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Mystical , physical , alchemical
♫ We 're pretending to be in love today
♫ But pretending is also real
♫ There 's a lady in a castle
♫ She 's sad and so forlorn
♫ When her troubadour returns and kisses her
♫ She 's all smiles and laughter
♫ Lady , you 're so beautiful
♫ Come lie with me and be my love
♫ I 'd slay any dragon , endure any danger
♫ Just to have you near me
♫ Love is a magical thing
♫ Lucky lovers mate in the spring
♫ We sip from goblets full of joy
♫ But when love dies all life it does destroy ♫